RESUME

Rajashri Mahapure (Master Of Computer Application)

Mobile No: +91-9152139418 Email: mahapure.rajashri@gmail.com

Objectives

4 years 6 months of professional experience in Web Development and Database Creation. Seeking a responsible position in an organization which gives me the chance to improve knowledge and enhance my skills and enable me to strive towards the overall development of the organization. Obtain a challenging leadership position applying creative problem solving and management skills with a growing company to achieve optimum utilization of its resources and maximum profits.

Professional Experience		
Working For: Pulse solutions, Jogeshwari.		
Duration	From January 2018	
Job Profile	PHP Developer	
Working For : Webian Tech	nnologies Pvt. Ltd,Thane.	
Duration	August 2017 to October 2017	
Job Profile	Software Developer	
Working For : Saga Solutions And Consultancy, Pune.		
Duration	June 2015 to September 2016	
Job Profile	Software Developer	
Working For : Compile Time Solutions, Pune.		
Duration	Jan 2015 to June 2015	
Job Profile	Software Developer	

Educational Qualification			
Course	University	Percentage	Year of Passing
M.C.A.	Pune University	65.57%	2015
B.C.A.	Pune University	68.25%	2012
H.S.C.	Maharashtra State Board	51.83%	2009
S.S.C.	Maharashtra State Board	77.69%	2007

Technical Skills		
Programming Languages	JAVA, ANDROID	
RDBMS	SQL Server 2005and Above, MS-ACCESS, MySQL, Sqlite, Ms-Sql	
Web Standards	HTML, CSS, XML, PHP., Wordpress	
Scripting Languages	JAVAScript , Jquery, AJAX	
O.S	Windows 98/NT/2000/XP and Above	
Framework	Codeigniter	
Tools Used	Notepad, Notepad++, Sublime text, Putty, FileZilla, SVN	

Technology Experience	
PHP, HTML, CSS, SQL Server, MySQL, Ms-Access	4 Years
Codeigniter, Javascript, JQuery, Ajax	4 Years
Java, Android, core php	6 Months
Drojecte Done	

Project III:Pulse Solutions	
Title	Command51
Role	Developer

Description

Web application for the ARPA membership for the animal rescue.ARPA provides the opportunity for animal welfare professionals from organizations across the country to connect, share, learn, educate and ultimately combine their resources towards improving animal welfare industry overall.

URL:- https://www.animalrescueprofessionals.org/

Project II:Pulse Solutions	
Title	Animal Rescue Professionals Association(ARPA)
Role	Developer
Description	

Description

Command 51 is the web application user for delivering quality services, catering to their client needs. This helps to maintain the scopes, specifications and attendance schedules. it integrates the clients, Subcontractors, Managers, Integrations. Helps to keep the details report about the survey of cleaning works respective to each client.

URL:- https://secure.command51.com.au/login

Project I: Pulse Solutions	
Title	Doobert
Role	Developer
D	

Description

Doobert is about bringing together Animal rescue volunteers and Rescue and shelter organizations to save animals. Doobert technology powers your passion for animals and allows you to choose how to get involved.

URL:- https://www.doobert.com/

Project III: SagaSc	
Title	Saga Solutions & Consultancy
Role	Developer
Description	
Static website designed & developed for Saga Solutions & Consultancy having home, about us,	
contact us, careers, blogs, services and product details.	

Project IV: SagaSc		
Title	PMS(Project Management System)	
Role	Developer	
Description		
It's a web b	It's a web based application used to Manage Leave, Attendance, Tickets, Bugs, Scrum of SagaSc.	

which is used for employees of SagaSc. Also manage project details from client side for and creating invoice and quotation In PDF format according to project details.

Project V: My Car	
Title	Leave Management System
Client	MY Car, Pune.
Role	Developer
Description	

customer requirements.

My car is a car seller company having 6 branches in Pune. Leave application manage the all employees' attendance as per shift changes, generates monthly salary sheet company wise or as per department.

Project VI: Nexa	
Title	Nexa E-Quote
Client	MY Car, Pune.
Role	Developer
Description	
This is a Web application used to create the quotation in the form of PDF with respect to	

Project VII: Pune In My Pocket	
Title	Pune In My Pocket
Client	Compile Time Solutions, Pune
Role	Developer
Description	

This is a mobile application having all information related to Pune city like, hotels, tourist places, helpline numbers, news, time tables of S.T., Train, flight scheduler to & from Pune.

Role And Contribution

Developer

- Understand the business and functional requirements and analysis.
- Database creation.
- Development of reusable code.
- Development and implementation of core functionality and support tools.
- Iterative testing and code reviews through development of the application.
- Library implementation PHPExcel, mpdf, dompdf, payment gateway.
- Integration Testing & debugging.
- Aws server handling.

Personal Details		
Gender	Female	
Date of Birth	21st, March 1991	
Nationality	Indian	
Marital Status	Married	
Parent/Guardian's Name	s Name Mr. Virendra Mahapure.	
Address	Room no. 166, DR. Ambedkar Nagar, Near Muktabai Hospital,	
Address	Bhatwadi, Ghatkopar(West), Mumbai-400084	

Declaration

	I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true and correct t	o the best of my
knowl	edge.	

Thank	You,
-------	------

Date: / / Rajashri Mahapure